How is this possible
Lewes
Stop trying to scare us
We've already tested it
The frogs are fine
The weight gain is obvious
The formula
Has no issues at all
The feed is fine
But it's illegal
I've already reported it
Ms. Zoe
This is bad
The Market Supervision Bureau said
In our feed
There are prohibited substances
They've shut down the factory
We're ruined
How could the factory be shut down
It's you
You're the one behind this
Lewes
You ruined my plans again
I'll kill you
Who dares touch my husband
I'm from the Verdant Town Police Station
Zoe
Daniel
You're suspected of producing and selling
Unsafe
Food additives
You are under arrest
Come with us